<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>posts on me.shew.io</title><link>https://me.shew.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in posts on me.shew.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 21:01:54 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://me.shew.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>poetry is my passion</title><link>https://me.shew.io/posts/poetry-is-my-passion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 21:01:54 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://me.shew.io/posts/poetry-is-my-passion/</guid><description>&lt;pre tabindex="0">&lt;code>this ive learned:
human brain is wired to two things
- finding patterns
- searching for meaning
and confusing the two
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre></description></item><item><title>Bored outta my mind</title><link>https://me.shew.io/posts/bored-outta-my-mind/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:28:21 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://me.shew.io/posts/bored-outta-my-mind/</guid><description>&lt;p>Among my various mild mental maladies is a sincerely ingrained fear of boredom.
There’s two severity layers to the fear:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Anxiety of being idled and potentially missing out on some form of consumption
or recreation&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Severe anxiety of being forced to be minimally stimulated and attentive
without being able to disengage for long periods of time&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>While the latter is just something I’ve come to work around in life, the former
is a trained response. I know for a fact I didn’t have it before the age of 12
and at some point between my teenage years and my adult life, I lost the ability
to be comfortably bored. I think at some point as my responsibilities grew and
my sanctioned free time shrunk, I came to associate idleness with some
opportunity cost.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>write, bro, write</title><link>https://me.shew.io/posts/write-bro-write/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 21:33:21 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://me.shew.io/posts/write-bro-write/</guid><description>&lt;p>I’m forcing myself from the time I’ve started writing this to not switch
contexts. From the time it took me to start that last sentence to the time I
finished, I stood up and went to watch a Monster Hunter Wilds video my wife
wanted to show me. :v:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’ve got a very strong desire to write more entries for this space I’ve made,
but I have this massive inertia to just start and iterate on the ideas I wanna
capture. I’ve got this idea now, though, that if I just start writing as if I
were yapping in-person to someone, then it’ll be way easier to build that
writing muscle.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Some October Polaroids</title><link>https://me.shew.io/posts/some-october-polaroids/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://me.shew.io/posts/some-october-polaroids/</guid><description>&lt;p>Late last year, I deep-dove into instant photography. The original idea in my
head was to start blogging and journaling various projects I&amp;rsquo;d be working on at
a time. The aesthetic of journaling and scrapbooking projects like garage
experiments really settled nicely in my head. After all of that, I ended up
buying a Polaroid Now+ and very quickly came face-to-face with the hardships of
taking good, clear photos of awkward subjects without any studio setup.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://me.shew.io/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://me.shew.io/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>After writing this site for ages, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally plopped down and hashed it out
in a few days, neglecting to do much of anything else in the process.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As of right now, the site&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple &amp;ndash; not as lean as I&amp;rsquo;d like it, but it
gets the job done. I&amp;rsquo;ve still got to finish up the summary and resume page of
the site which will require me dusting off my resume and thinking hard about
what it is I want this site to expose about me.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>